<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog for Learning on Data Science Community Site</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog for Learning on Data Science Community Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RStudio Community Monthly Events - January 2022</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-01-25-rstudio-community-monthly-events-january-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-01-25-rstudio-community-monthly-events-january-2022/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Jong Marshes on Unsplash
Welcome to RStudio Community Monthly Events Roundup, where we update you on upcoming events happening at RStudio this month. Missed the great talks and presentations from last month? Find them listed under ICYMI: December 2021 Events.
You can subscribe to the Community Events Calendar so that new events will automatically appear on your calendar. Please note that by subscribing, all of the events in the calendar will appear on your own calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Start an Internal Data Science Community</title>
      <link>/blog/2021-01-25-build-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021-01-25-build-community/</guid>
      <description>This post is based on Rachael Dempsey&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn post on starting a data science community at your organization.
 Find a core group to start Centralize the team &amp;amp; information (Zoom/Slack/Teams channel) Be persistent and hold meetings regularly Standardize events to eliminate some of the work in planning Demonstrate value and ROI internally Build enthusiasm by showing completed projects to get others involved and word of mouth will help you grow  Photo by Sean Patrick from Pexels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Steps to Successfully Bring Open-source Tools to Your Team</title>
      <link>/blog/2021-01-25-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021-01-25-open-source/</guid>
      <description>This post is based on Rachael Dempsey&amp;rsquo;s LinkedIn post on bringing open source tools to your organization.
Talk to IT.  IT is concerned about the security of the comapny. The team wants to understand potential security concerns, precedence, why open source is an enterprise asset. It is helpful to write up a document making the case for R to your IT dept. Be persistent but understanding. Want to learn more?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
